Let me explain some context about the DPAP, so DPAP is basically a data protection application
programming interface.
So it's key, basically it's one of the Windows security architectures, so one of very powerful
Windows security architecture, because the credential managers, like the credential managers
basically using the DPAP key and encrypting the data and it will be storing inside of that,
and we are using the browser-based credentials, like we will be saving in a browser data
flight, probably like passwords from here, so this all will be, this all the things
will be saved, managed by using the DPAP data protection API, like data protection API keys,
okay, probably the browsers like Chrome, Edge, and a few other browsers using the data
API key, data protection application API keys and the WISHY passwords also will be saved
using the DPAP API, and also few other encryption tools will be also using your DPAP API, so
the context is, if you already extracted the DPAP API, so you can able to dump the browser-based
credentials or any credentials that has been stored under the credential managers or any
things, okay, so that was the small context, so overall understanding, it's like one
of a powerful security architecture is to protect the passwords, like in a browser or any login
data in a browser, also it will be protecting the window certificates later things, yeah,
these are the few things we will be using the DPAP API to protect the data, okay, so if someone
crack your DPAP API, basically we'll be getting a DPAP API from else as dumb, so if the attacker
sorry, if the attacker has a DPAP API key, so the attacker can able to easily decrypt the username and
password from the browser, okay, so we will be seeing how to decrypt the data that has been stored
in a browser in the next video, so so now I hope you have a better understanding about the DPAP
initially, let's hop off and we'll connect you in our next video, thank you guys, bye-bye.